there's something we need to discuss
with you but you have to swear on the
bible that this stays between us
this has the new testament format and
the prequel for jake john forget the
goddamn bible yes sir
we are making a play against christian
and if you side with us you will have
more money
and power than you ever dreamed of
congrats
your days of doing grunt work are
finally over from this moment forward
you are no longer
junior executives in training you're now
senior executives in theory
all you have to do is walk out that door
[Music]
actually we decided we like where we're
at you guys just seem
really stressed out all the time with
very little power comes very little
responsibility
we're buddhists now well sucks to be
you then you're gonna have more money
and power whether you like it or not and
a bigger office
i like this office how do you like it
now
huh
what more
ouchy ouch
welcome to the inner circle you're all
here
because we trust you or because you were
standing nearby when we were trying to
recruit somebody else
and it would have been awkward not to
invite you kevin
christian is a psychopathic dictator who
has run this company into the ground
i think we can all agree i will be a
more democratic leader so
without further discussion let's move on
our job today
is to build a case against christian
that kate and i can present to the board
tomorrow
so we need to make a list of everything
he's done wrong
we only have one white board good point
matt jake fetch us some more whiteboards
i thought we weren't doing any more
grunt work
see if you're crying for bath time like
the rest of us
you